{
  "questions": [
    {
      "category": "GENERAL",
      "question": "What is Celestia?",
      "answer": "Celestia is primarily an Anime Trading Card Game with an RPG inspired battle system for your Discord server. Collect your favorite characters, level them up, and fight with them in various PvE and PvP gamemodes. ||Also, why does everyone keep asking \"What is Celestia\", but no one's asking \"How is Celestia\"...||"
    },
    {
      "category": "GENERAL",
      "question": "I have a great idea for the game, how can I tell you about it?",
      "answer": "Awesome! Please use the in-game command ```/celestia contact suggest```. In order to file a suggestion, you must be at least Rank 5."
    },
    {
      "category": "GENERAL",
      "question": "I found a bug, how can I tell you about it?",
      "answer": "Please use the in-game command ```/celestia contact report``` and follow the instructions in your DMs. In order to file a report, you must be at least Rank 5."
    },
    {
      "category": "GAMEPLAY",
      "question": "Why does card XY not have a Unique/Special Ability?",
      "answer": "When creating new cards, we try to design the skill-set as close to their actual abilities as possible. The occasional creative off-tracking aside, we try to avoid adding abilities we aren't 100% comfortable with. While that might sound a bit anticlimactic, please take into consideration that we revisit \"older\" cards once in a while and see if we can rework them (changing/adding abilities, adjusting stats, etc.) so they fit into the current state of play. If you think there is a character that got robbed of their full potential nonetheless, feel free to send us a suggestion."
    },
    {
      "category": "DONATIONS",
      "question": "Is there a way to support you?",
      "answer": "Yes! You can support us by telling more people about Celestia! Please also consider donating so we can cover the maintenance and hosting costs for Celestia and this website. As a small thank you, every person donating **$5 and above** receives an in-game 'Donor' tag on their profile."
    },
    {
      "category": "DONATIONS",
      "question": "What does a 'Donor' tag come with?",
      "answer": "null"
    },
    {
      "category": "DONATIONS",
      "question": "Is it possible to gift someone a 'Donor' tag?",
      "answer": "null"
    },
    {
      "category": "DONATIONS",
      "question": "I haven't received anything after donating, what should I do?",
      "answer": "null"
    },
    {
      "category": "DONATIONS",
      "question": "Can I get a refund?",
      "answer": "Yes, you can! If you have accidentally donated the wrong amount or want to cancel your donation for any other reason, contact us within 48h after making that donation via emailhere[at]email.com. We'll get in touch with you for further procedure."
    },
    {
      "category": "MISC",
      "question": "How did you decide on the name?",
      "answer": "Truth to be told, we were looking for a cute cards-related profile picture for Celestia's Discord client and stumbled across an artwork of Celestia holding a card in her hand. Call it love at first sight, call it we-didn't-look-any-further-because-we're-lazy, but we just decided to go with it."
    },
    {
      "category": "MISC",
      "question": "I have a question that isn't listed here.",
      "answer": "Shoot us a DM on Discord, we'll try to reply as fast as possible. For serious inquiries, please use our email: emailhere[at]email.com"
    }
  ]
}
